### **SKILLS & ABILITIES**

Certified in Full Stack Web Development through UCF with proven experience in HTML, CSS, and full stack JavaScript. Proficient at contributing to a highly collaborative work environment and finding solutions. Exceptional knowledge of the best practices for web design, user experience, and speed.

### **EDUCATION**

High school graduate with some college experience UCF Full Stack Bootcamp Graduate | September 2022 to December 2022

## **EXPERIENCE**

### Field Service Technician

CSC Service Works | March 2018 to Aug. 2022

- Provide expert level diagnoses and repair while ensuring the highest level of customer satisfaction
- Responsible for my own territory/company locations
- Troubleshooting mechanical and technological repairs, and proactively managing maintenance requirements to keep machines working reliably, reducing the need for future service calls
- Maintaining a stock of parts in your company vehicle so you're always prepared to provide a quick solution and caring for your vehicle as if it were your own

## Lead Warehouse/Machine Prep/Lead Installer/Restoration

CSC Service Works | Feb. 2017 to March 2018

- Managed and maintained safe and efficient teamwork of multiple job sites daily
- Received shipments, organized, prepared, removed and installed equipment
- Complete all work with the highest level of customer care

## Warehouse Team Member/Installer

CSC Service Works | Nov. 2016 to Feb. 2017

Responsible for receiving shipments as well as preparing, delivering and installing equipment at properties for new and existing customers.

# Warehouse/Machine Prep/Installation

Aaxon Your Total Laundry Solution | June 2016 to Nov. 2016

Responsible for preparing all machines with power cords, card readers, programming and gas conversions before being shipped to buyers or installed on routes. Ensure a clean and professional installation on routes by leveling all machines, installing water hoses, gas lines and dryer venting followed by making sure that all machines run properly. Maintain the organization of warehouse stock on a daily basis.

## Assistant Manager/Operations Manager

Off The Wall Trampoline Fun Center | April 2014 to June 2016

Responsible for the employee schedule consisting of over 80+ workers. Maintaining assets to the company such as inventory and counting the daily balance as well as cash deposits. Work to ensure the satisfaction of every guest's happiness.